

Personal Description

A little information about myself I am a final student majoring in informatics engineering at the University of Lampung with a GPA of 3.43 and domiciled in Bandar Lampung. I am a responsible person, honest, interested in technology curious about this field, have a high willingness to learn, quickly adapt well to new environments, and can work individually or team. I have expertise in the area of IT and have experience building websites understand several programming languages (PHP, HTML / CSS, Python, Laravel Framework, C++, etc.) can operate Microsoft Office



jl hj abdul muis tuan ria lk 1 Rt/Rw 002 kel langkapura baru kec langkapura Gg bukit VIII. No.52 Bandar Lampung

Experiences

PT. Micsrosoft Indonesia Mar 2021 - Sep 2021

Studi Independent Learning Track Cloud Fundamental

- build a final project (capstone) with the theme of education moodle on cloud azure
- complete all available learning related to the Azure Fundamental Cloud Track with a satisfactory value

PT. Bisa Artifisial Indonesia (Bisa.AI) Mar 2022 - Aug 2022

Internship BackEnd Developer

- re-develop the BackEnd on the Tampil.id web application
- added additional features to the Tampil.id project in the BackEnd section
- complete the learning available on e-learning Bisa.ai and get certification
- Participate in available webinars and get certificates

Kementrian Sosial (Pejuang Muda)

Internship

- Collect data on residents for beneficiaries with the SAGIS application
- Build a forest honey project to be empowered by the local community

Language

Indonesia: Native

English : Intermediate

Hobby

Basket

Music

Otomotif

Education

SMAN 7 Bandar Lampung 2014 - 2017

Organization:

- Osis
- Basket

Universitas Lampung

2018 - 2022

Organization:

- HMJ Himatro
- Basket

Skills

Hard Skills:

Microsoft Office Competen Laravel Github/Gitlab Python HTML PHP CSS MySQL ΑŃ java

JS

Competen **Intermediate** Intermediate Intermediate Intermediate Intermediate Intermediate Intermediate Beginner Beginner

Soft Skills:

Adaptability Communication Problem Solving Teamwork Creative Crtitical Thinking analytic

Contact Person



zikriahmad805@gmail.com



085378984983



linkedin.com/in/ahmad-zikri-3a7b03232



https://github.com/ ahmadzikrill